Hey there, my name's Cristian and I help e-commerce brands create product pages that
are incredibly fast and smooth for their customers.
In the next minute, I'll show you a quick before and after.
And you'll see the exact performance improvements that we get.
Lighthouse Report. Now,
since this is the unoptimized version of the web page,
we have an image that's much too large.
We have layout shifts. As you can see here,
we have a script running in the background. background. That makes the site slow
and clunky for users to navigate through. And all these lead to,
as you can see here, a performance of 38.
Where we get a largest contentful paint of 12 seconds,
a total blocking time of 570 milliseconds,
and a cumulative layout shift of 0.139.
All of which not only your users don't like,
but Google doesn't like either. And it  pushes your site down below everybody else's
on the web search rankings. Luckily,
however, all these problems are completely fixable.
Here, I'm going We have the same website,
same layout, same font, same description,
same everything. Except this time,
when we run our Lighthouse report, since this is our optimized version,
we have an image that actually fits and is to scale.
We have no layout shifts happening anywhere within the site.
And we defer all background scripts that are not important to make it feel
fast and quick to navigate. Leading to,
as you can see here, a performance of 100.
Or we have a much better LCP of 0.7 seconds.
We have a TBT of 0 milliseconds and a CLS of 0.
All of these lead to a professional and quick-feeling website  that your users love
and Google loves to. Putting your website at the top of  all the web
search rankings. Now I want to make this as simple and transparent
for you as I can. Everything I did to get this optimized page,
you can get in my PDP conversion pack. Where I'll give you a core
vitals audit and quick-wins  list, image font and script optimization,
structure data and SEO schema fixes, and complete before and after report,
and a 10 minute loom walkthrough, just like we're doing right now.
If any of this sounds useful for your website, your business,       I'd be more
than happy to give you a quick, no obligation plan.
Just click here on get a fixed price, fill out the information,
and I'll get back to you, I'll review your website,
and I'll send your response within a day or two.
Thanks so much for watching. My goal is simple, to help you create a.
My goal is simple, to help you create a faster, more stable, higher converting
storefront, and I'd love to help you with exactly that.
I'm looking forward to hearing from you.